<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ICCC2016</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hotel_and_travel">Hotel/Travel</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="fragment_hotel_title1">Hotel Information</string>
    <string name="fragment_hotel_title2">About the Hotel</string>
    <string name="fragment_hotel_title3">Ground Transportation</string>
    <string name="title_activity_program">Programs</string>
    <string name="icon_font_welcome">&#xe6c8;</string>
    <string name="icon_font_program">&#xe614;</string>
    <string name="icon_font_map">&#xe626;</string>
    <string name="icon_font_patrons">&#xe6ea;</string>
    <string name="icon_font_commitee">&#xe6bd;</string>
    <string name="icon_font_hotel_and_travel">&#xe71f;</string>
    <string name="icon_font_message">&#xe645;</string>
    <string name="icon_font_version_update">&#xe60f;</string>
    <string name="title_activity_patron">Patrons</string>
    <string name="icon_font_patron_huawei">&#xe789;</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="title_activity_committee">Committee</string>
    <string name="welcome_title">WELCOME</string>
    <string name="title_activity_version">Version</string>
    <string name="welcome_content">\tOn behalf of the Executive Committee and the hosting University of Electronic Science and Technology of China,
        it is our great pleasure to welcome you to the fifth IEEE/CIC International Conference on Communications in China (ICCC 2016) in the magnificent
        city of Chengdu, China, 27-29 July, 2016.\n\n
        Since its commencement in 2012, the ICCC conference has grown steadily from a brand new conference with
        a strong vision, to a unique venue in bringing together global researchers and practitioners in areas of communications to the greater China region.
        In particular, this year’s ICCC aims at addressing a key theme on “Ubiquitous Communications &amp; Computing for Future Internet”,
        which broadly cover all disciplines of communications from fundamental research to emerging applications, while emphasizing society-shaping
        technologies in the modern IT era.\n\n
        In addition to providing a major forum for people to present their frontier research work and discuss the
        latest breakthroughs, the ICCC 2016 also features Keynotes, Plenary Speeches, Invited Talks, Tutorials, Industrial &amp; Academic Panels,
        Exhibitions, and dedicated Workshops. For those who attend the ICCC for the first time, you will soon appreciate the fact that ICCC is more
        than just an outstanding technical conference, it is also a friendly rendezvous to interact, inspire, and discover.\n\n
        This year we are honored to have four world renowned scholars to be our keynote speakers. Not only have each of them made extraordinary
        contributions to the fields of communications, their diverse expertise and keen visions in both academia and industry are equally remarkable.
        We look forward to their stimulating and scholastic seminars.\n\n
        Finally, we wish all the participants a very fruitful and productive conference, and also an unforgettable stay in Chengdu.</string>
    <string name="welcome_end">Program Committee, IEEE/CIC ICCC 2016</string>
    <string name="update_info">Already up-to-date</string>

    <string name="huawei_introduction">Huawei is a leading global information and communications technology (ICT) solutions provider. Driven by responsible operations, ongoing innovation, and open collaboration, we have established a competitive ICT portfolio of end-to-end solutions in telecom and enterprise networks, devices, and cloud computing. Our ICT solutions, products, and services are used in more than 170 countries and regions, serving over one-third of the world\'s population. With more than 170,000 employees, Huawei is committed to enabling the future information society, and building a Better Connected World.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">Detail</string>


</resources>
